<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>burger king Archives - mybkexperience</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/burger-king/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/burger-king/</link>
	<description>BurgerKing survey at mybkexperience.com</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 07:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">192922290</site>	<item>
		<title>Chicken Curry Recipe</title>
		<link>/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/</link>
					<comments>/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 07:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger king]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chicken Curry Recipe: Ingredients: 1 1/2 lbs boneless chicken, cut into bite-sized pieces 2 tablespoons oil 1 onion, chopped 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 inch ginger, grated 2 tomatoes, chopped 2 teaspoons coriander powder 1 teaspoon cumin powder 1 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon chili powder (optional) 1/2 teaspoon salt (or to taste) 1 cup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/">Chicken Curry Recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-114 size-full" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/cck.jpg?resize=275%2C183&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="275" height="183" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p>Chicken Curry Recipe:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.googleadservices.com/pagead/aclk?sa=L&amp;ai=DChcSEwjoosTer4D9AhUK10wCHdbgDysYABAAGgJ0bQ&amp;ohost=www.google.com&amp;cid=CAASJeRojZskLRJeeqINVe2pOPxHR3bzA6ReKdVZqJoAr223smQ66RA&amp;sig=AOD64_2ig2CEEIg-87lBHrCHp6N14oKAeA&amp;q&amp;adurl&amp;ved=2ahUKEwj3wbrer4D9AhWd4HMBHZXgAC0Q0Qx6BAgHEAE">Ingredients:</a></p>
<ul>
<li>1 1/2 lbs boneless chicken, cut into bite-sized pieces</li>
<li>2 tablespoons oil</li>
<li>1 onion, chopped</li>
<li>3 cloves garlic, minced</li>
<li>1 inch ginger, grated</li>
<li>2 tomatoes, chopped</li>
<li>2 teaspoons coriander powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon cumin powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon turmeric powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon chili powder (optional)</li>
<li>1/2 teaspoon salt (or to taste)</li>
<li>1 cup chicken broth</li>
<li>1/2 cup heavy cream</li>
<li>Fresh cilantro leaves, for garnish</li>
</ul>
<p>Instructions:</p>
<ol>
<li>Heat the oil in a large saucepan over medium heat.</li>
<li>Add the onions and cook until soft and translucent, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Add the garlic and ginger and cook for another minute.</li>
<li>Add the chopped tomatoes and cook until they have broken down and the mixture has thickened, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Add the coriander, cumin, turmeric, chili powder (if using), and salt. Stir to combine.</li>
<li>Add the chicken pieces and cook until they are browned on all sides, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Pour in the chicken broth and bring to a simmer.</li>
<li>Reduce the heat to low, cover the saucepan, and cook for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.</li>
<li>Stir in the heavy cream and heat until the sauce has thickened slightly, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Serve hot, garnished with fresh cilantro leaves. <a href="/mybkexperience-survey/">Enjoy!</a></li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/">Chicken Curry Recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">113</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Homemade Pasta Recipe</title>
		<link>/2022/11/23/homemade-pasta-recipe/</link>
					<comments>/2022/11/23/homemade-pasta-recipe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 14:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger king]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Let&#8217;s prepare some spaghetti at home! You can make it right now if you have flour, two eggs, a little olive oil, and salt. To produce excellent handmade pasta, you don&#8217;t need special Italian pasta flours, and it&#8217;s okay if you don&#8217;t have a pasta maker. Using a simple rolling pin and your hands, you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2022/11/23/homemade-pasta-recipe/">Homemade Pasta Recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-105" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/images-1.jpeg?resize=469%2C311&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="469" height="311" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p>Let&#8217;s prepare some spaghetti at home! You can make it right now if you have flour, two eggs, a little olive oil, and salt. To produce excellent handmade pasta, you don&#8217;t need special Italian pasta flours, and it&#8217;s okay if you don&#8217;t have a pasta maker. Using a simple rolling pin and your hands, you can produce pasta. I frequently make pasta at home, and this is now my go-to &#8220;everyday&#8221; recipe. It produces a wonderful, adaptable dough that you can roll out and shape into different types of noodles.</p>
<p>This <a href="/mybkexperience-survey/">page</a> contains my basic pasta dough and process. The fundamentals. Aside from that, I&#8217;m going to give you a good earful. I&#8217;ll go over some variations and considerations further down. I&#8217;ll also include step-by-step photos of the pasta dough-making process. You can make it by hand, stand maker, or pasta maker. Homemade <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=pasta&amp;rlz=1C5CHFA_enIN987IN987&amp;sxsrf=ALiCzsb85Yn05o8PwbVbKXE5KGpvhla05w:1669214744257&amp;source=lnms&amp;tbm=isch&amp;sa=X&amp;ved=2ahUKEwi294m_xcT7AhVJS2wGHaXiBbUQ_AUoAXoECAEQAw&amp;biw=1440&amp;bih=789&amp;dpr=2">pasta</a> recipe is one of my absolute favourite things to make, and I&#8217;ve compiled everything I&#8217;ve learned about it over the years into this single post, complete with links to my favourite resources. This is an ongoing journey for me, so I&#8217;ll keep you updated. Have fun and happy pasta making!</p>
<p><strong>How to Make Eggless Pasta</strong></p>
<p>I&#8217;m sure many of you will want to know how to make eggless pasta or vegan pasta dough. No worries. I make a dough similar to this for one of my favourite pasta shapes, pici. Essentially, you cut 1/4-inch strips of dough and roll them out by hand. Eggless doughs like this are typically used for shapes like pici, cavatelli, trofie, and orecchiette rather than pasta noodles like the others we&#8217;re focusing on today. To make eggless pasta dough, follow these steps: 200g &#8220;00&#8221; flour, 200g semolina flour, 200g warm water, and 1 teaspoon fine grain sea salt are combined. Use these ingredients and follow the &#8220;How to Make Pasta By Hand&#8221; instructions in the book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2022/11/23/homemade-pasta-recipe/">Homemade Pasta Recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/11/23/homemade-pasta-recipe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">103</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Burger King Job Openings</title>
		<link>/2021/12/11/burger-king-job-openings/</link>
					<comments>/2021/12/11/burger-king-job-openings/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 05:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger king]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=61</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to get a burger king job? Go to the burger king website. Navigate to the career option(It is located down the website). Click on Opportunities below Careers- You land on the process possibilities page. Here, you may see the variety of in-eating place jobs Burger King appears for maximum times. Tap on every possibility [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2021/12/11/burger-king-job-openings/">Burger King Job Openings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-8 size-full" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/mybkexperience-survey-1.jpg?resize=550%2C302&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="550" height="302" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/mybkexperience-survey-1.jpg?w=550&amp;ssl=1 550w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/mybkexperience-survey-1.jpg?resize=300%2C165&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 550px) 100vw, 550px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p><strong>How to get a burger king job?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Go to the burger king <a href="https://www.bk.com/">website.</a></li>
<li>Navigate to the career option(It is located down the website).</li>
</ul>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-62 size-large" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/bk-careers.png?resize=1024%2C696&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="1024" height="696" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/bk-careers.png?resize=1024%2C696&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/bk-careers.png?resize=300%2C204&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/bk-careers.png?resize=768%2C522&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/bk-careers.png?w=1028&amp;ssl=1 1028w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<ul>
<li>Click on Opportunities below Careers- You land on the process possibilities page.</li>
</ul>
<p>Here, you may see the variety of in-eating place jobs Burger King appears for maximum times. Tap on every possibility to realize the only that works for you, its responsibilities, qualifications, and skills. Now, scroll to the lowest of the Opportunities web page and click on the Find a Restaurant and Apply button.</p>
<ul>
<li>Lastly, navigate to a prospected job and the location that works for you and apply.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Eligibility of Burger King jobs</strong></p>
<p>Burger King has 4 main process roles for you if you want to paintings in-restaurant. The posts are specifically a Team Member, an Hourly Shift Coordinator, an Assistant Manager, and a Restaurant General Manager.</p>
<p>These are human beings <a href="/about-mybkexperience/">Burger King</a> is typically searching for. For starters, to paintings at Burger King, you want to be age sixteen years and above. However, this relies upon the function you play inside the restaurant.</p>
<p>Sixteen years is the minimum age for a Team Member. For 3 of the opposite roles listed, you need to be 18 years and above. But this isn&#8217;t all this is required. Each of those jobs has its process descriptions and qualifications, that you should meet. The popular necessities are as follows.</p>
<p>You ought to be resilient. Here, you ought to be capable of paintings in a completely rapid environment. Also, be capable of paintings for longer hours, weekends, and holidays. Have great visitor provider abilities.</p>
<p>You will address humans all of the time from clients to visitors at your restaurants. Therefore, you ought to have appealing human abilities to have interaction with humans greater correctly and professionally. Good management abilities. If now no longer a crew leader, any of the opposite 3 roles, you may be in fee of humans and teams.</p>
<p>Your cap potential to oversee the ones below you is essential. Burger King will need to recognize whether or not you&#8217;ve got got a few enjoy in dealing with humans. Possess great control abilities. The 3 pinnacle roles require which you have great control abilities, specifically operations, humans, and accounting.</p>
<p>Burger King gives you the hazard to paintings with them at any in their locations. Go to the respective websites in distinctive countries, then visit their careers page. Find a process becoming your competencies and description, practice for it, and await Burger King’s comments. Hopefully, you get suitable comments and begin running immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2021/12/11/burger-king-job-openings/">Burger King Job Openings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2021/12/11/burger-king-job-openings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">61</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Burger King just added a new burger to their $ 1 menu</title>
		<link>/2021/11/02/burger-king-just-added-a-new-burger-to-their-1-menu/</link>
					<comments>/2021/11/02/burger-king-just-added-a-new-burger-to-their-1-menu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 06:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger king]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[menu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=50</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It can be a great way to run your money on fast food restaurants and still leave happy. Next to the rodeo burger. The Rodeo Burger offers fried onion rings and hot, spicy BBQ sauce on a Whopper Jr. patty in a sesame bun. The Rodeo Burger will replace the Bacon Cheeseburger on the Economy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2021/11/02/burger-king-just-added-a-new-burger-to-their-1-menu/">Burger King just added a new burger to their $ 1 menu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-8 size-full" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/mybkexperience-survey-1.jpg?resize=550%2C302&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="550" height="302" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/mybkexperience-survey-1.jpg?w=550&amp;ssl=1 550w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/mybkexperience-survey-1.jpg?resize=300%2C165&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 550px) 100vw, 550px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p>It can be a great way to run your money on fast food restaurants and still leave happy. Next to the rodeo burger. The Rodeo Burger offers fried onion rings and hot, spicy BBQ sauce on a Whopper Jr. patty in a sesame bun.</p>
<p>The Rodeo Burger will replace the Bacon Cheeseburger on the Economy menu and is the first change to the $ 1-Your-Way menu since its debut in 2020. The $ 1-Your-Way menu now includes Rodeo Burgers, Jr Chicken Sandwich., French fries, and a 16-ounce drink. Rodeo Burgers on the $ 1 Your Way menu at participating locations across the country.</p>
<p>The best bargains on the <a href="/">Burger King</a> menu right now include special fries prices, the original chicken sandwich, the Croissan&#8217;wich sandwiches and of course the Whopper. Prices range from $ 1 to $ 20, but as of late 2020, the chain is adding a few items to the new $ 1 menu based on your preferences.</p>
<p>Head to BK on Dec 28 for a cheeseburger and classic bacon, Jr. chicken sandwich, french fries, or an inexpensive lemonade for just $ 1 at a limited price The chain isn&#8217;t afraid to point out its competition, saying unlike others (tip: the dollar menu at <a href="https://www.mcdonaldsindia.com/">McDonald&#8217;s</a>), everything on this menu is strictly US $ 1. (Related: McDonald&#8217;s Makes These 8 Important Improvements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2021/11/02/burger-king-just-added-a-new-burger-to-their-1-menu/">Burger King just added a new burger to their $ 1 menu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2021/11/02/burger-king-just-added-a-new-burger-to-their-1-menu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">50</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: mybkexperience.website @ 2023-07-08 09:56:40 by W3 Total Cache
-->