<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized Archives - mybkexperience</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/uncategorized/</link>
	<description>BurgerKing survey at mybkexperience.com</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 16:29:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">192922290</site>	<item>
		<title>KFC burger recipe</title>
		<link>/2023/02/25/kfc-burger-recipe/</link>
					<comments>/2023/02/25/kfc-burger-recipe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 16:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Once upon a time, Colonel Sanders had a secret recipe for a mouth-watering burger that he had perfected over the years. The recipe included 11 herbs and spices, but no one knew what they were. One day, a young chef named Ron discovered the recipe while cleaning out the basement of an old KFC restaurant. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2023/02/25/kfc-burger-recipe/">KFC burger recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-90 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/033_FR11785.jpeg?resize=300%2C200&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="300" height="200" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/033_FR11785.jpeg?resize=300%2C200&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/033_FR11785.jpeg?resize=768%2C511&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/033_FR11785.jpeg?w=1000&amp;ssl=1 1000w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p>Once upon a time, Colonel Sanders had a secret recipe for a mouth-watering <a href="/mybkexperience-survey/">burger</a> that he had perfected over the years. The recipe included 11 herbs and spices, but no one knew what they were.</p>
<p>One day, a young chef named Ron discovered the recipe while cleaning out the basement of an old <a href="https://online.kfc.co.in/">KFC</a> restaurant. He was amazed by the unique blend of flavors and decided to recreate the burger.</p>
<p>Ron worked tirelessly, experimenting with different ingredients and cooking techniques until he finally replicated the burger exactly as the Colonel had intended. He presented it to his bosses at KFC, who were blown away by its deliciousness.</p>
<p>The burger became an instant hit with customers, who flocked to KFC to try the secret recipe for themselves. It was unlike anything they had ever tasted before, and soon, KFC&#8217;s sales skyrocketed.</p>
<p>Ron&#8217;s discovery of the secret recipe had transformed KFC&#8217;s fortunes, and he became a hero in the company. He was promoted to head chef and given free rein to experiment with new recipes, which he continued to do for many years.</p>
<p>To this day, the KFC burger remains a beloved fast food staple, enjoyed by millions around the world. And although the secret recipe is still a closely guarded secret, one thing is certain: its unique blend of herbs and spices is what makes it truly special.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2023/02/25/kfc-burger-recipe/">KFC burger recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2023/02/25/kfc-burger-recipe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">119</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chicken Curry Recipe</title>
		<link>/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/</link>
					<comments>/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 07:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger king]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chicken Curry Recipe: Ingredients: 1 1/2 lbs boneless chicken, cut into bite-sized pieces 2 tablespoons oil 1 onion, chopped 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 inch ginger, grated 2 tomatoes, chopped 2 teaspoons coriander powder 1 teaspoon cumin powder 1 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon chili powder (optional) 1/2 teaspoon salt (or to taste) 1 cup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/">Chicken Curry Recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-114 size-full" src="https://i0.wp.com/mybkexperience.website/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/cck.jpg?resize=275%2C183&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="275" height="183" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p>
<p>Chicken Curry Recipe:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.googleadservices.com/pagead/aclk?sa=L&amp;ai=DChcSEwjoosTer4D9AhUK10wCHdbgDysYABAAGgJ0bQ&amp;ohost=www.google.com&amp;cid=CAASJeRojZskLRJeeqINVe2pOPxHR3bzA6ReKdVZqJoAr223smQ66RA&amp;sig=AOD64_2ig2CEEIg-87lBHrCHp6N14oKAeA&amp;q&amp;adurl&amp;ved=2ahUKEwj3wbrer4D9AhWd4HMBHZXgAC0Q0Qx6BAgHEAE">Ingredients:</a></p>
<ul>
<li>1 1/2 lbs boneless chicken, cut into bite-sized pieces</li>
<li>2 tablespoons oil</li>
<li>1 onion, chopped</li>
<li>3 cloves garlic, minced</li>
<li>1 inch ginger, grated</li>
<li>2 tomatoes, chopped</li>
<li>2 teaspoons coriander powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon cumin powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon turmeric powder</li>
<li>1 teaspoon chili powder (optional)</li>
<li>1/2 teaspoon salt (or to taste)</li>
<li>1 cup chicken broth</li>
<li>1/2 cup heavy cream</li>
<li>Fresh cilantro leaves, for garnish</li>
</ul>
<p>Instructions:</p>
<ol>
<li>Heat the oil in a large saucepan over medium heat.</li>
<li>Add the onions and cook until soft and translucent, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Add the garlic and ginger and cook for another minute.</li>
<li>Add the chopped tomatoes and cook until they have broken down and the mixture has thickened, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Add the coriander, cumin, turmeric, chili powder (if using), and salt. Stir to combine.</li>
<li>Add the chicken pieces and cook until they are browned on all sides, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Pour in the chicken broth and bring to a simmer.</li>
<li>Reduce the heat to low, cover the saucepan, and cook for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.</li>
<li>Stir in the heavy cream and heat until the sauce has thickened slightly, about 5 minutes.</li>
<li>Serve hot, garnished with fresh cilantro leaves. <a href="/mybkexperience-survey/">Enjoy!</a></li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/">Chicken Curry Recipe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2023/02/06/chicken-curry-recipe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">113</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Beef for Stovetop Burgers</title>
		<link>/2022/07/11/the-best-beef-for-stovetop-burgers/</link>
					<comments>/2022/07/11/the-best-beef-for-stovetop-burgers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mybkexperience]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=80</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; The Best Beef for Stovetop Burgers After messing around adding this and that to ground beef in my quest to make a better burger, I finally realized that it really is all about the meat. Buy good meat and you will have a great hamburger. It&#8217;s that simple. (Also, keep an eye out for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2022/07/11/the-best-beef-for-stovetop-burgers/">The Best Beef for Stovetop Burgers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h1 style="text-align: center;">The Best Beef for Stovetop Burgers</h1>
<p>After messing around adding this and that to ground beef in my quest to make a better burger, I finally realized that it really is all about the meat. Buy good meat and you will have a great hamburger. It&#8217;s that simple. (Also, keep an eye out for good quality ground beef offerings &#8211; you can stock up and freeze the formed burgers for later meals.</p>
<p>The ideal ground beef for burgers should be 80% lean and 20% lean, but often 85% lean and I think that still makes great burgers.Avoid anything with less than 90% fat &#8211; these burgers can easily get dry and crumbly.</p>
<p>If possible, buy fresh ground beef from the butcher. Not only does it tend to be a bit fresher than corned beef, but it&#8217;s also less compressed. A light hand results in a tender <a href="/2021/11/02/burger-king-just-added-a-new-burger-to-their-1-menu/">burger</a>. Don&#8217;t worry if you only have frozen beef you can still make a decent burger this way.We have some tips and tricks for defrosting ground beef.</p>
<p>How to Form and Shape Patties Perhaps more than the fat content or quality of the meat, I&#8217;ve found that a light touch can make the real difference between a burger I enjoy eating and one that comes out chewy. Puree the meat while forming the patties, the more compressed and chewy the finished patty will be.</p>
<p>Instead, try to handle the meat as little as possible when forming the patties. Break off large, fist-sized pieces from the minced meat and press them with the palm of your hand on the work surface into coarse patties .Gently tap the edges to give them an even round shape. Don&#8217;t worry if the edges look a little lumpy or cracked; Resist the urge to keep the burgers looking clean and tidy. These blemishes are all in the name of an overly tender burger.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.kitchenfoodcompany.com/">Kitchen Food</a> Managing Editor, Christine Gallery, taught us the whole dimple trick and I haven&#8217;t looked back since. Making a shallow indentation in the center of the burger will prevent the burger from shrinking in size and turning brown. in the middle of .After years of small, round burgers, this feels like magic. To make an indentation in your burger, simply use your fingertips to dab the center of the burger patties slightly thinner than the outside edge, maybe half an inch flatter max. .Always think of finished patties as looking like small ones look like frisbees.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2022/07/11/the-best-beef-for-stovetop-burgers/">The Best Beef for Stovetop Burgers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">mybkexperience</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/07/11/the-best-beef-for-stovetop-burgers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">80</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: mybkexperience.website @ 2023-07-08 09:56:38 by W3 Total Cache
-->